<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="story_content">
        <item>

       A Story From England
            \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t

           The story starts with a description of Kimberly Clark, the protagonist of the story, who is twenty-five years old with all qualities of a normal young woman. She is pretty, she loves to dance, and she has many friends and a good position in the office of a large company. Despite these all, she has a problem.
            She has been troubled by a strange and mysterious dream that haunts her every night.

            \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            The strange dream always begins on a country road. Kim stands on this road and sees a lane with a white fence and a hedge on each side.
            At the end of the lane, on the top of a little hill, she sees a small white cottage with green shutters.
            Then she walks up to the lane to the house, goes in and looks around. In one of the rooms, she finds a man asleep in bed. He is a little old man with white hair and a white beard. When she comes near his bed, the man wakes up. Then he sits up and looks at her. When she tries to speak to him, she wakes up.
            She is very troubled by the dream because she has never known any little old man like that and neither the place.
            \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            Kim’s roommate knows everything. So, one day she asks Kim to visit her (Janet’s) parents’ farmhouse to feel peace in mind. As they pass through a country road, Kim sees a similar scene which she sees in her dream. They stop there.
            Janet does not want Kim to go and see the small cottage but Kim goes.
           \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            The house was exactly the same, except for a sign ‘FOR SALE’ in front of the house. Unlike her dream, Kim goes to the door of the house and knocks and to her surprise, the same old man answers the door who immediately closes the door. After Kim’s request, he opens the door. Kim again asks why the house is for sale. The old man reveals that the house is haunted by a ghost. Kim tries hard to think to say something instead asks who the ghost is.
            The old man gets surprised and shocks her by replying that she herself is the ghost.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
        </item>
        <item>
            A Story From Colombia
             \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            The only child of Roberto and Rosa Soto was Maria del Carmen. She was beautiful. She was bright, kind, and loving but she was always sick. By the time she turned four, she was very weak and died a few days later. After Carmen’s death, Rosa gave away Carmen’s things to the local priest of the other village because the doctor had said that they would not have the next child. However, Roberto had hope.
            Rosa thought that it was only false hope.
              \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            As Roberto was looking out to the backyard where Carmen often played, he remembered a little doll which Carmen used to play with. It was not given to the priest and was in Carmen’s hand when she died. Rosa also did not know about it and neither did Roberto. They looked everywhere and asked friends, the neighboring children, and even the undertaker but nobody knew about the lost doll.
            So, they forgot about it.
             \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            On the first anniversary of the death of Carmen, Rosa gave birth to another baby girl proving that the doctor was wrong. The baby girl was baptized ‘Evangelina’ that meant ‘good news’. She was same as Carmen in appearance, action, and characters. The big difference was that Evangelina was healthy.
            The priest even thought that God took their sick child, healed her, and gave her back to them.
            \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            One day when Evangelina was four, she said that she had been sick long ago. She even told to her aunt who was from Bogata. They did not give more attention to her thinking because she knew about Carmen by learning from her parents. During their conversation, Evangelina said that she knew about the doll. She took her mother and her aunt into the backyard and asked her mother to dig up hard, strong ground next to the tree.
            To their surprise, they found the lost doll under the ground.
            \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            Evangelina said that when she was sick, the priest came and prayed. Then she went to sleep but a real nice man woke her up. He did not let her take her doll with her. She wanted to bury the doll in the yard.
            So, he helped her put it under the ground without a shovel. Rosa was speechless.\n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\

        </item>
        <item>
            A Story From German
            \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            The story took place on 26th December 1903 in Berlin, Germany. The famous German surgeon, Dr. Emil Braun, was sitting alone in the dining room of his apartment trying to write notes about the surgery while having his dinner. Soon he dozed off but woke up when he heard the doorbell ring. He heard a child talking about her sick mother to Mrs. Braun. He went to the door and saw in the semidarkness a little girl of perhaps six or seven who was wearing a cotton dress and shabby shoes. Over her head, she had a ragged shawl which she was holding together at the neck.
            The doctor felt sympathy for the child and her sick mother and became ready to go with her.
            \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            It was raining lightly outside as the doctor walked down the steps to the street but the girl was already almost a block up the street, waiting for him. She walked too fast, however. Stopping only for a moment at each corner to make sure he saw where she was going. The girl led the doctor through the poorest part of Berlin, the section of the city around the hospital where Dr. Braun was a head surgeon. Finally, they reached an old tenement house where the girl’s mother was living. The doctor climbed upstairs up to the fifth story.
            As the doctor entered the room, he heard the door close softly behind him.
          \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            The woman was lying in bed. The doctor recognized her as a person who at one time worked as the maintenance staff at the hospital. She was suffering from pneumonia.
            When the doctor talked about the girl, daughter of the woman, Elda said that her daughter, Adelheid,
            had died of the flu in September just three days after her seventh birthday.
            \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            The doctor was surprised. The little girl was not there. Elda told that she had kept Heide’s shoes and shawl to remind her of Heide. The doctor got up and looked. He saw the same ragged shawl on a hook and a pair of shabby shoes on the floor.
            As he looked closely he found them wet. Elda said that she had been thinking about him earlier that night hoping and praying for him. As she was talking she fell asleep.
            Then, touching her feverish head once more, he took his black bag, stepped out into the dark hallway, and closed the door. \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
        </item>
        <item>
            A Story From Mexico
            \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            Though the story Fear is from the unit of the supernatural stories, it is not a supernatural story. In fact, it is a psychological story. It’s a thriller or suspenseful story based on human fear of a nervous man.
            This story also shows how a man behaves in a state of panic and nervousness.
            \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            The main character of the story is Armando Gonzalez. He was a man who had to look after a big family of nine members. However, he had a dream. It was a common dream to have a house of his own.
            With this aim, he had saved 50,000 pesos for the last many years (20 years).
                       \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
On that very day, he went to the bank to withdraw 50,000 pesos because he had seen a house within that limit. The deal was finalized and he had to do the payment. He was very careful from the beginning. The bank was slightly crowded that day and he did not like it. In his turn, the bank accountant started to count the money loudly which Armando did not like.
            He feared other people would know that he was carrying a heavy amount and anybody could loot him.
                                    \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
He caught a bus to go home. There he met a man whom he had already seen in the bank. Not only that he had dashed against him and he had given a double look at Armando Gonzalez. Here, he found the same man getting on the same bus. Now, there was no doubt to Armando that man intended to rob him. Everybody in the bus was looking at him only because he was putting his hat backward. But, what Armando thought was that they were looking at him because they had the knowledge that he was carrying 50,000 pesos.
            He started to see a thief on each face. This increased his nervousness all the more.
                                               \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
After some time, he found that the man was talking to three other boys. He thought that they were making secret plans to loot him. This heightened his nervousness and he made a plan to get off the bus at the next stop and to take another bus from there and he did accordingly. Suddenly, he also saw that the same three boys had got off there. Now, it was sure to Armando that it was a part of the robbery. Now, he was panic-stricken. He started to run shouting for help. The three boys also started to run after him only with the intention to help him. But, there was no limit to Armando’s fear and he was running as fast as he could. Suddenly, his feet got entangled with something and he fell down. Before he got up, the three boys came up to him. Armando started to implore / beg / plead them not to rob him. They were also surprised at it and they said that they were not intending to loot him.
            Rather they were students and they were there for a football tournament and that they were running after him because he was shouting for help.
                                                           \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
Now, his fear is gone and he got up and put his cap on and this time he put it rightly. At this time, all the four walked up slowly back to the street.
                                                                   \n
                                                                        \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\



        </item>
        <item>
            A Story From Japan
             \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            Mr. Shoji Sakota was a pharmacist in the city of Sappora on Hokkaido island in northern Japan. He used to have his own drug store in the same building, where he used to live.
            He used to live alone in the rear part of the building because his wife had died several years earlier.
            \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            One stormy winter night in 1964, he was working in his room at about midnight. As it was the end of the fiscal/financial year, he was very busy with the profit, loss and the accounts of the whole year. At that time, there was a knock at his door. At first, he avoided it. But the knocking persisted or repeated. At last, he opened the door thinking that somebody might have come for some very important medicine. It was a woman who wanted an ame (Japanese candy used for pacifying young children) on a stick for her baby. Mr. Sakota was quite surprised at it because the lady was buying sweet at that time of night. He was very much moved or surprised by the appearance of the lady.
            She was so strange that her hair was disheveled/messy/uncombed/untidy and her eyes were quite strange.
            \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            In short, she looked at a lady from another world. The lady went from there but somehow or other Mr. Sakota could not forget her appearance and at last he left working and went to the bed. On the next night, the same woman came and both the times she asked for an ame. Mr. Sakota was all the more worried. He had a friend with whom he shared his worries. The friend was a photographer.
            So, they planned to snap the lady if she came the next time or next night.
             \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            The next night also, the lady came at the same time and with the same demand. The photographer friend was hiding in the shop and he snapped the lady from different angles. But, when the photographs came, they were quite surprised to find that all articles were present in the photograph but not the lady.
            Then the two friends decided to follow her the next time if she came.
            \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            The next night also, the lady arrived at the same time and asked for an ame. When she left the shop, the two friends followed her quietly.
Finally, they reached a room in an old building. In the room, they found a baby sucking or licking an ame and the woman appeared to be sleeping there in the bed.
            When they tried to wake up the lady, they realized that she was dead and they felt that she had been dead for several days.
            \n
             \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            The conclusion is that after her death the lady’s soul was worried about the child. She not only wanted to arrange for food for her child but she also wanted someone to come and know that she had been dead and her child was in a helpless situation.
            She had selected Mr. Sakota for this.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
        </item>
        <item>
            William Wordsworth
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            “My Heart Leaps Up When I Behold” is a poem written by a famous nature poet William Wordsworth. In this poem, the poet recollects/remembers the experience of his childhood days and gives his emotion and feelings a meaning. The poet also expresses his love for nature. He feels great joy when he sees a rainbow in the sky. He used to enjoy a lot when he saw the rainbow in the sky in his childhood.
            He hopes he will still get pleasure at seeing the rainbow when he becomes old and if such feeling stops in the future he wishes to die.
                       \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
According to the poet, the child is the father of man because childhood is the beginning of the manhood. In other words, the qualities of the grown-up men are all derived from childhood. At last, the poet wishes that his remaining days would be bound by his love for nature.
           \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            A paradox is a statement containing opposite ideas that make it unlikely although it may be true. The above statement is paradoxical in the sense that it contains opposite ideas for normal people. The child cannot be the father; he is the man who can be the father. But, the poet through his statement “The Child is the Father of the Man”, wants to say that childhood is the beginning of manhood. The thing we do and feel as children affect the way we feel when we are adults.
            The poet also wants to say that the present is the result of the past.

        </item>
        <item>
           Barbara Holland
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            The essay “Speaking of Children” is an extract from Barbara Holland’s renowned volume Mother’s Day or the View from In Here. In this essay, HHolland examines the idea of having more than one child and its effect on the parents. She believes that one child is an appendage but more than one is a way of life. One child is outnumbered and parents can brainwash it, carry it to parties, toss it on the bed with the coats and make it whatever they want. It is usually easy to look after one child. It is a part of their lives.
            But, plural children are a counter-culture in the house. Parents are outnumbered by the children.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            In other words, parents must accept or do something they do not want but they are compelled to do certain undesired things. They have to buy many toy sets and they can not go to the weekend where they like. They have to move to better schools for their children. They have to be involved in many social converse/talk/discussion. They are pushed backward. Above all, they have to lose peace and privacy because they are frequently interrupted by their children. Then, there is a bitter look in every one. When there is secrecy, they have to talk on the phone from their office. In this way, the children will not let the parents talk peacefully and privately. Even the plural children can become a real danger for a family because many marriages break up in AAmerica justdue to the children. As a whole, mothers of plural children have no peace in their life. They have to sleep with startling suddenness and finality or determination.
            So, this essay is against having many children.\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
        </item>
        <item>
           Patricia Hampl
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            “Look At a Teacup” is an essay written by the feminist writer of America, Patricia Hampl. This essay is written in the narrative style which narrates the history of feminism in America. The two major themes of this essay are the relationship between the mother and her daughter (the author) and the connection between the past and the present.
            Both of these themes are represented by the teacup.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            In this essay, there are two different stories. The first story is the essayist’s mother’s story. The mother married in 1939 with an American who had been born in Czechoslovakia. She had bought china cups and plates for her marriage. These cups and plates were made in Czechoslovakia and they are beautiful. In fact, she was very happy in the world of her cups and plates. For her, marriage and the family were the most important things in life.
            Many years later, she gave these cups to the writer because the writer is her daughter.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            The second story in this essay is the story of the Second World War, which also started in 1939. Many things fell that year. Basically, ‘that year’ means the time of war that caused many things to fall, for example, human bodies fell dead in the streets by falling bombs. Countries, cities, industries and a lot of other things fall. Even Czechoslovakia stopped the production of beautiful teacups. In this period, bombs fell on innocent women and children. Thus, women in America revolted against the crime and atrocities done on women. They considered the crime as male oppression and tyranny against women. This is why women’s liberation movement started. The women of this new generation show their anger by rejecting old traditions. They consider work as the most important thing in a person’s life. So, marriage and family lose their importance because feminists take it as a kind of slavery. Teacups are no more a symbol of marriage and family life for the writer but they are actually the symbols of the war against women. On the other hand, the essayist’s mother used to emphasize the family. Even the mother wanted her daughter to get married.
            The essayist thinks the past is very important but her mother thinks it is the future that matters.\n
                        \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\

        </item>
        <item> Eudora Welty
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            The story “A Worn Path” is about an old black woman called Phoenix Jackson. She used to live in a village far away from the town. She had no one except a grandson. He was very sick so she had to go to the town at regular intervals to bring medicine for her grandson.
            The town was very far from her village and the journey was really very difficult.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            This story describes one of her such journeys to the town. On the way, she has to face many obstacles. But, every time she faces the obstacles very boldly and at last, reaches to the town. Her journey starts through the hill. It being December, it was very cold and the pathway was covered with snow. She tapped her stick on the snow and continued her journey.
            She used to talk to herself most of the time and she also talked with all the animals that she met on the way.
           \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            After climbing the hill with great difficulty, now she had to climb down but by then she got caught by thorny bush with great labor she freed herself and again continued her journey. After sometimes, she came by a creek. She had to cross it. It was not an easy job. She had to cross it through a log. She took it to be a trial. Very carefully, she crossed the creek. She crossed it through a log even with her eyes closed. She again continued her journey but there was another obstacle waiting for her. Now, she had to cross through a barbed-wire fence. She crept and crawled through the wire saving herself and her gown. Again, she faced trouble successfully. Now, she was passing through a cornfield. There she saw a scarecrow. At first, she thought it to be a ghost but very boldly, she talked with it. Finally, when she knew that it was a scarecrow, she even danced with it. After crossing the cornfield as she was going on her way from somewhere, a black dog came before her all of a sudden. She lost her balance and fell down in a ditch there.
            She raised her hand for help. But, as there was nobody around, she silently remained there.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            After some time, a hunter came there. He took her out from the ditch. While talking, a nickel (five-cent coin) dropped down from the man’s pocket. She stole it with a trick. After some time, she reached the town. There she asked a lady to tie her shoelaces. The whole town was decorated with colorful bulbs. But, her eyes were not working properly because it wasn’t broad daylight. But, depending on her senses, she finally reached the medical clinic. There she even forgot why she had been there. She didn’t remember for a short time. However, while talking with the nurse, she remembers her grandson and her purpose of visit. She took medicine. While she was going from there, she got a nickel as a gift. She said that she would buy a paper toy for her grandson.
            After that, she left the clinic.  \n \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\

        </item>

        <item>Ernest Hemingway
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            The “The Three Day Blow” is a love story written by Ernest Hemingway. The protagonist of this story is Nick, who has a beloved named Marge. Both are passionately in love but lately, they have quarreled and Nick has sent her away in anger. He feels that it is his mistake so he is very unhappy at present. He is also depressed and dejected because he has lost hope of seeing his beloved again. Thus, a kind of storm is blowing in the psyche of Nick and he has no sense of peace, silence, and tranquility. In other words, he has become completely restless.
            For this reason, he goes to meet his friend Bill so as to get relief from his restlessness position.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            Bill lives with his father in a cottage on the hill top. It is autumn season and the weather is wet. Autumn storms have started and at this time, a storm is blowing. It is very cold. When Nick has just reached the cottage, Bill opens the door and comes out. He warmly welcomes Nick inside and they sit down in front of the fire. Luckily, Bill’s father is not at home. They start talking about games and they also start drinking whisky. After that, they talk about the taste of whiskey and drink again and again. Again, they talk about many different things like books, writers, fishing, baseball, drinking, etc. They even talk about their own fathers each time they fill their glasses with whiskey and drink. Ultimately, the drinks heat them and they get quite drunk.
            To some extent, for a time Nick has forgotten his inner storm of depression and dejection.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
             However, suddenly, Bill speaks about Marge again and praises Nick for breaking the relationship. Quite contrastingly, the storm again starts blowing inside Nick’s mind and he becomes completely impatient and intolerant. On the other hand, Bill does not understand about Nick’s inner thoughts. He even warns Nick not to go near Marge again because the relationship may start again. This warning and caution becomes a hint for Nick. Now his desperation and hopelessness vanishes and there is again hope for a reunion or reconciliation. In fact, Nick had never thought about this. So, Bill’s warning makes him happy but he does not say anything to Bill. Rather, Nick himself decides to go
            just to meet Marge after the end of the three-day autumn blow that is considered to be physical blow.
                        \n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\


        </item>
        <item>William Cowper
             \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            The poem “The Poplar Field” is about natural conservation.
            Through this poem, he wants to give a message that it is not good to chop down trees.
            But, it’s not only that. It also compares the chopping down of trees to a man’s life and death.
            From this point of view, this poem is also philosophical.
                        \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            This poem starts with the description of a forest and the changes that have come after the trees are cut down.
            With the trees, all the attractions of the place have gone. Neither there is the shade nor there is the sweet
            music of birds nor is even the wind playing there. Then the poet says that he will die very soon but before his
            death certainly a new jungle will not take place instead of trees that have cut down. He says that the pleasures
            of man are not permanent or not long-lasting. Rather, they are shorter than short human life. They finish before
            a man dies. To sum up, the poet means to say that he used to get a maximum amount of pleasure from the poplar trees
            but his pleasure has been snatched away from him.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\



        </item>
        <item>Isaac Asimov
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            The essay “The Nightmare Life Without Fuel” was written by an American writer Isaac Asimov.
            In this essay, the writer predicts the cold, dark and dirty life of the world people due to the fuel crisis.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            It is a rainy day of 1997 when the resources of the fuel have already been used up. As a result, there is scarcity in the means of transportation. Instead, feet have become the safest and easiest means to move. Demolition has become the best job because the wooden and metals structure used in the pulled down houses can be used again. There is no alternative source of energy.
            Driving automobiles has become a matter of pas because of the increase in the price of gasoline.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            The fuel crisis has certain advantages too. When the vehicles stop running in the street and the factories stop operating; the air will become cleaner. When there is no pollution in the environment fewer people will catch a cold. Since the criminals won’t be able to use the means of transportation; the crime rate will go down. There will be mutual protection in the crowd. Above all, the legs will be the king of the cities. In the time of the fuel, crisis people have to manage their life with some substitutions. Air Conditions (AC) will be substituted by open air.
            Room heaters will be substituted by warm sweaters and Lukewarm sponge bath will substitute a hot shower.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\

            The condition of the suburbs will be worse than that of city centers. They were born with the auto, lived with the auto and now they are dying with the auto.
In the time of fuel crisis railroads and subways will get major attention because they can best transport coal and people respectively.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            As America struggles without fuel, the condition of other countries in the world will be worse. The world population has reached 5.5 billion, out of which only 20% population (1.1 billion) will get sufficient food to eat. The rest of the population will suffer from starvation. After the bodies of the mothers go dry, their babies starve to death. It will only increase the Infant Mortality Rate (IMR). Two billion populations, on the other hand, will suffer from only to keep their bodies working. As a result, their mind will be permanently damaged.
                       \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
People will be left with no means of entertainment. They will have to work and sleep; Eating will not be guaranteed. Machines will be replaced by human muscles and beasts of burden. There will be starvation, violence, and disease which will reduce the world population to less than a billion.
                        \n \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\



        </item>
        <item> W. S. Merwin
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            In the essay “Unchopping a Tree”, the writer presents an impossible example to convey deep meaning. Joining the chopped parts of trees refers to the new plantation of more trees in the open fields, which are full of stumps. Every part of trees refers to every part of nature whether they are small or big. Each and every part of nature is important. As we are also the creation of nature, it is our duty to maintain the balance in nature. We don’t have rights to destroy nature. Actually we are not destroying nature but we are destroying ourselves. Our lives totally depend upon nature. Through the writer’s appeal to join the parts of the chopped trees,
            he wants to remind human beings about their important works to be done to conserve the greenery of nature.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            Unchopping a tree is impossible. It is only a kind of feeling but certainly, it has meaning. The writer emphasizes the preservation of nature. Nature should be preserved and those persons who cur the trees must plant some more in replacement. When they save and plant the trees, it is unchopping a tree. The writer warns that it is easy to destroy but very hard to create. He further says that the life of a tree and human life are the same so they should be preserved with equal emphasis. Not only the trees we should save but also should protect the habitats of some animals who live in trees. The writer tries to persuade us how to work hard to bring the chopped tree into the original situation, which is not really possible. When a tree is felled down, there is no way to bring it into its original condition. But its place can be replaced with more trees, which we plant. Trees are also important parts of the ecosystem as other living creatures. We should think of conservation of such trees instead of
            deforestation for the protection of the ecosystem.
                      \n  \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\



        </item>
        <item>
            Mark Strand
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            The poem “Keeping Things Whole” was composed by a Canadian poet Mark Strand. In this poem, the poet pleads for unity, integration, and
            wholeness against the usual fragmentation that takes place in everyday life.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            The world and the people in it have been divided into many fragmentations due to politics, religion, economy, caste system and geography. The fragmentation has given rise to the sense of alienation, exile and identity crisis. The poet in the poem “Keeping Things Whole” feels the same; when he goes he finds himself missing. As he walks, he causes fragmentation in the air. The fragmented air moves back to fill the space where his body has been. All the people in this world have different reasons for
            moving but the poet moves to keep things whole.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            In the poem “Keeping Things Whole” the poet might be trying to tell us that fragmentation is the usual process that keeps in taking place all the time. Though we claim to bring unity, integration, and wholeness among things and people, it is useless because we ourselves are the agent of fragmentation. Our involvement in different social, political and religious situations inevitably invites fragmentation among people.
                        \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\



        </item>
        <item>Dorthi Charles
           \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            The poem “Concrete Cat” is composed by Dorthi Charles merely for the eye but not for the brain and emotions. This unique poem is the physical appearance of the cat rather than in words. This poem implies about the cat and its catness in action. The ear, eye, mouth, whisker, tail, etc. all have been sketched on the page to denote both abstract and physical meaning. The pun in the cat’s middle stripe is the only place where language aspires towards poetry and becomes figurative. The middle stripe shows the stomach part which says much about the human world and human activities. The term ‘mouse’ that is upside down indicates the image of a dead mouse.

         \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
The poem is very funny and like a puzzle game. A cat can be drawn by connecting lines. Every word is a part or organ of a cat. The ears are pointed upward, eyes show sign of wonder and mouth is at the sight of the dish. The tail is moving happily. The overall effect of the poem is funny as well as philosophical.

        </item>
        <item>
             Roger Rosenblatt
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            “Oops! How’s That Again?” is a humorous essay written by Roger Rosenblatt. In this essay, the writer classifies verbal errors in 5 categories and tries to explain the causes behind search errors.
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            Slip of tongue is the most common type of verbal error. They occur when a speaker means to say one thing but happens to say something else. They are usual and can take place all the times. They create an embarrassing effect on both the speaker and the listener. Example of tongue slip was made by a businessman Peter Balfour in a dinner party where he wished just engaged Prince Charles a long life and conjugal happiness with Lady Jane. But in fact, Prince Charles was engaged to Kady Diana and Lady Jane was his former beloved.
                       \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
The second type of verbal error is Faux Pas. It takes place when somebody says something it to be harmless but its meaning upsets the listener. Example of Faux Pas was made by German president Henrich Lubke who greeted the Indian President at the airport as “Who are you?”. He meant to say “How are You?” but end up of saying “Who are you?”.
                                   \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
The third type of verbal error is Blooper. It is a public blunder like the one spoken over the radio. Unlike tongue slip and faux pas, it can have a long term effect on the listener because the mistake is delivered to a large number of audiences. One example of blooper was made by Chicago’s Mayor Daley. Once he said, ” The policeman is not there to create disorder, the policeman is there to preserve the disorder.” It was very difficult for him to recover from this public blunder.
                         \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\

            The fourth types of verbal error are Mistranslation. It takes place when certain slogans and statement are translated from one language to another carelessly. A slogan “Come alive with Pepsi” failed considerably when it was translated into German as “Come alive out of the grave with Pepsi.”
                         \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
The last type of Verbal error is Spoonerism. It takes place when the initial or other sounds of the word are interchanged with the sound of another word. An example of spoonerism is “Kinquering Kongs Their Titles Take” (Conquering Kings Their Title Take.”
                         \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
A Linguist, Victoria Fromkin regards the slip of tongue as the clues to how the brain stores and articulates language. The famous psychologist Sigmund Freud regards tongue slip as the means for expressing repressed desires.
                         \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
A psychiatrist Richard Yazmajian argues that there are some incorrect words in the associative chain which are to be substituted by correct word. When we say something carelessly the incorrect words are expressed along with the correct word so we make mistakes.

                         \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
Though all of us make mistakes while speaking, we laugh when we hear somebody making mistakes. It is because it breaks the monotony and refreshes us We laugh at the mistakes also because we enjoy looking at the changing appearance of the speaker. Sometimes verbal errors reveal the repressed desires of the speaker and they sometimes express the optimistic note of the speaker as well.
                       \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\

            Our life is full of mistakes of one type or another. Any deviation from what we expect is an error. All of us want to be immortal but everyone has to die sooner or later. So we are confused by our mortality and laugh at each other.
                        \n \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\







</item>
        <item>Rabindranath Tagore
            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            Malini is a poetic play written by Bengali Indian poet and philosopher Rabindranath Tagore. This play is a story of love and hatred that deals with the religious conflict between Hinduism and Buddhism in the state of Kanshi.
\n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            Malini is the princess of Kanshi, though born in a dogmatic Hindu family, she has adopted Buddhism because Buddhist monks taught her. Because of her faith in Buddhism, she wants to live a simple life, untouched with royal luxuries, beautiful clothes,
            and valuable jewellery that would suit her beauty and youth.The Hindu brahmins feel threatened with the new creed of Malini and are demanding for her banishment. On the other hand, Malini herself wants to be banished so that she can lead the wanderers to their destinations.
\n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
Kemanakar is one of the Hindu brahmins who strongly demand Malini’s banishment. On the other hand, Supriya, the childhood friend of Kemanakar, sees no reason for banishing an innocent girl like Malini. He also believes that the force of numbers of people cannot determine truth.
\n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
King’s army is taking the side of the Hindu’s; the Hindu brahmins do not want to get the victory using the armed force. They believe that their faith will make them victorious. When they start praying to their guardian gods and goddesses, Malini appears in front of them. Malini tells them that she has exiled from the palace at their demand. The Hindu brahmins get impressed by the words and appearance of Malini and start praying to her as their goddesses.
\n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
The holy people who are not impressed by Malini are Supriya and Kemanakar. Supriya, too thinks that he has found his faith in the form of Malini because he is not satisfied with the gods of books. On the other hand, Kemanakar thinks that Malini and her religion are just an illusion like moonlight that disappears in the midday sun. When Kemanakar becomes alone in this great fight, he decides to go to a foreign land to get the help of foreign soldiers. Supriya too wants to follow him, but Kemanakar asks Supriya to live in Kanshi and keep him informed.
\n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
The second part of the play opens in the garden where Malini and Supriya are talking. During the conversation, Malini wants to learn about Kemanakar from Supriya. He told that Kemanakar was his friend. Kemankar has been firm and strong, while his thoughts are always flickering with doubts. He also reveals that he has deceived his friend, informing his plan to the King.
            Unlike Supriya, Kemankar is strong both in his words and his actions. He is determined to wash away Buddhism from the state of Kashi at the cost of his own life. He is ready to sacrifice his life for his religion. Even Malini praises him like a god. The main difference between Supriya and Kemankar is that Supriya is ready to sacrifice his life and religion for Malini, whereas Kemankar is ready to sacrifice his own life for his religion.
\n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
On the last part of the play, The king enters he is very much happy with Supriya, and he proposes Supriya to ask even Malini. But he refuses all things from King. He only wanted love from Malini, which she has for every creature in the world.

Kemankar has been captured by the King’s soldier and is going to execute him. Malini and Supriya plead the King to pardon him. As his last wish, Kemankar asks his friend Supriya why he betrayed him.
\n
\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\


        </item>
        <item> Harold J Morowita
\n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            Dr Harold J Morowita is a professor of Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry. He is a scientist, teacher, and author. ‘The Six Million Dollar Man’ is a popular essay in which Morowitz examines the statistical statement that the chemical value of the human body is only 97 cents. He spends his essay in refining and improving the statement and tries to arrive at a more accurate definition at the end.

\n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            From a biochemical catalogue, he collects the information about the price of ingredients that the human body is made of. Then he calculates the average value of a gram dry weight of human being and his own dry weight. When he multiplies both, he finds his price, i.e. Six million dollar. But soon he realizes that each human being is priceless and infinitely precious. He concludes his essay with Alfred North Whiteheads conclusion that “ the human body is an instrument for the production at art in the life of the human soul.”

\n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\

            The author received a humorous birthday and from his daughter and son-in-law with a caption “ According to BIOCHEMISTS the materials that make up the HUMAN BODY are only worth 190 cents.” The definition compelled him to make a thorough study of the entire matter. He started by sitting down with his catalogue from a biochemical company and began to list the ingredients and their prices. His biochemical value was 97c when he was paying for the informally poorest form of cool, air, water, lime, bulk iron, etc. but in the six million dollar figure, he was paying for his atoms in
            the highest informational state in which they are commercially available.
           \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
It can be done for less than six thousand trillion dollars. But we cannot evaluate human life in a biochemical point of view. An incubator can develop micro-organisms artificially but it cannot assemble the cells into tissues, tissues into organs, and organs into a person, fill it with life and make a human being.
           \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
Thus, each human being is priceless and infinitely precious. We cannot evaluate a person’s life in terms of money. Rationality and humanity are the characteristics of human being. It can produce anything. Alfred North Whitehead is true that “ The human body is an instrument for the production of art in the life of the human soul.

            \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
Morowitz shifts his subject. He starts out talking about the human body and ends up talking about the human being. The human body and human being different from each other. The human body is made up of chemical organism but a man becomes a human being because of consciousness, rationality and some indispensable human qualities.
            \n \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\





        </item>
        <item>
           Arthur Guiterman
\n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t

            “On the Vanity of Earthly Greatness” is a poem written by Arthur Guiterman, an American poet and journalist, is best known for his humorous verse. Through humour, he has tried to depict the reality of human beings and animals caused by the change in time. It shows the bitter reality that the power of animals or human beings doesn’t remain the same when time and situation change. We always run after reputation and prestige. We become or want to be great and we think it will remain the same forever. We earn reputation and prestige and we think it will remain the same forever. We earn reputation and we think that the credit won’t be lost but actually we won’t think that is destroyed in due course of time. Our greatness is dismissed by time. So, time laughs at our blindness and pride.
\n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
Time is such a thing on which we cannot get the victory. Nature has given us limited time to live and exercise our power. Beyond that time, we cannot move according to our desire. Only in favourable time and situation, we can perform our actions or activities. The “vanity” actually means the degrading value of reputations of any persons and animals in the world. To clarify this point the writer has presented a few examples. Julius Caesar was a great warrior and a famous general statesman. He earned a great name and fame in his time through his strength and power. But that power lost its value with the change in the time and situation. He does not possess any arm and power to show his power of the past. His head is on the shelf and weapons and other things belongings are only in the museum in the form of history.
\n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
The roman emperor Charlemagne was great in his time by his sword, power. But the power of his sword also became meaningless due to the change in time. Now that sword has been rusted and is kept useless in the museum. Not only the great kings and warriors, but there is also a good presentation of powerful animals whose value has been decreased. Grizzly bear, whose embrace was very dreadful, has become nothing more than a rug to give warmth. Tusks of mighty brawls of mastodons have been changed into playing things like billiard balls.
           \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
All the given examples are concerned with the great but the greatness has been turned and reduced to valueless things. The vanity of human greatness and animals’ strength have become a good subject to present irony. That irony makes one feel unwell and quite indifferent to the person.
\n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
Everybody becomes great in his time and situation but later on, he becomes helpless and valueless. All reputation and achievements will be dismissed quickly. So, it is useless to take pride in one’s power as everything decays and fades away in due course of time.
\n
\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\</item>
<item>
    Joan Didion
    \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
    ‘In Bed’, an essay by Joan Didion depicts her personal experiences with migraine headache, which she inherits from her parents. She presents something unusual about the disease in a more philosophical and meditative domain of thought.
\n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
    Joan spends her day in bed there almost five times a month because of the migraine headache. She knows that she is going to be attacked by the headache when she feels some sort of irritation and flow of blood in the vessels of her brain. To avoid the attack she takes some medicines and starts to work. In her earlier days, she thought that she would get rid of the disease just by denying it. Sometimes she even tells lies saying that she did not have the attack frequently. But the truth was that sometimes the attack was quite violent and long-lasting. However, she feels good that she does not have any other physical problems, such as brain tumour, eyestrain or high blood pressure. She also tries to do all her normal work in spite of it. During the attack, her right temple (head) would suffer extreme pain and tears would roll down from her right eyes. She would also vomit. Generally, the headache may also be caused by stress, allergy, and tiredness, an abrupt change in blood pressure, a flashing light or a fire drill.
   \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
It’s strange that no medicine works effectively in case of migraine, especially when the attack begins. Some people may have a hallucination, blinding effect, stomach problem, tiredness and pain in all the senses along with headache. They are even unable to do their normal work. During the attack, Didion can’t see and speak clearly. She looks as if she has drunk some wine. But the headache never takes anyone’s life. It is interesting to know what doctors believe about a migraine sufferer. They said that the individual is ambitious, inward, and intolerance of unbearable pain But Didion’s untidy hair and carelessness in housekeeping do not point out her migraine quality. However, her great effort to write and rewrite a single paragraph for a week reveals some sort of perfection. Finally, she accepts the diseases and lives with them. When she has it she simply concentrates on the pain. But after ten or twelve hours she gets some sort of refreshment and spiritual power. She opens the window and feels the air, eats gratefully and sleeps well. She feels as if she is blessed by God. Therefore she is happy.
       \n \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
    \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\


</item>
            <item>
                Rudyard Kipling
 \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
                ‘The Gardener’ ends surprisingly revealing the reality of Helen, the protagonist, and her relationship with Michael. Michael, whom Helen calls nephew, is in reality, her son whose father is unknown throughout the story. The gardener is a mysterious character who does not appear at first and in the middle but only at the last of the story creating confusions in the readers. Helen Turrell conceals (hides) the truth about Michael till the end of the story but she does not show any reaction when the gardener confidently says he will tell where her son lies.
 \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
                The villagers of Hampshire believe Michael to be an unfortunate son of Helen’s late brother, George Turrell and his beloved (not wife). Actually it was not so. She had created a false story about Michael’s parents. Michael was born when Helen was in the southern part of France. She had told lies about her trip that she had long troubles. Because of the fear of social stigma she had told another lie that she had arranged for the passage of the child and a nurse from Bombay. She was thirty-five when she gave birth to the child. She showed much fondness to the child despite the fact that she was not the child lover.
 \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\



Michael was fearless, Philosophical, and fairly good-looking. At the age of six, he knew that Helen was not her real mother but his aunt. She did not allow Michael to say her mummy because she was unmarried. To escape from society’s contempt, she made Michael know a false reality.
 \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
Michael got maturity in due course of time but his interest in Helen was constant and increasing throughout. Though Helen wanted him to go to Oxford University, he took the war as his career. The First World War was going on. Many soldiers were killed during the war. Michael was killed by the shell-splinter explosion. After getting full proof about his death, Helen, being a next of –kin, prepared to go and see his grave in Hazenzeelein the third Military Cemetery with perfect information.

 \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
In a teashop, three kilometres away from the cemetery, she met an English Woman, Mrs Scarsworth. They stopped in a hotel where Mrs Scarsworth revealed that she had come there to see the grave of someone special to her and also that she was unmarried. Helen told a lie that she had come to see her nephew’s grave.
 \n
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
Next morning she walked alone towards the grave. As she was searching in the meantime she saw a man knelt behind a line of headstones-evidently a gardener. He did not introduce with her neither did he salute her. He asked her who she was looking for. She said it was Lieutenant Michael Turrell, her nephew. He had finite compassion in his expression and eyes. He said he would show her where her ‘son’ lay. She went away, supposing him to be the gardener when she left the cemetery.

                \n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\
\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\




            </item>








    </string-array>

</resources>
